<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<document>
	<title>More Life is a Terrible Album</title>
	<author>Sammie D.</author>
	<date>9/10/17</date>
	<photo>http://static.djbooth.net/pics-features/skepta-non-confirmation-of-drake-signing.jpg</photo>
	<content><![CDATA[ <p>As a person who listens to grime [read grime not Skepta] everyday, More Life is the worst album to come out in 2017. The sound selection and progression of the album is remarkably true to UK sound with Drake's (and 40's) spin on it. I think the songs are good. The problem with the album is that Drake made it and he is the one bringing UK music, in particular grime, over to the States.</p>

	<p>Discussion about the album has centered upon whether Drake is a culture vulture or not. Personally I agree that More Life isn't ablum, but a playlist and that Drake acted as a curator.But the debate of whether Drake stole or adapted UK culture is insignificant to what's actually happening. Drake determines current pop music. Pop music makes money. Every artists and label wants money. As we've seen throughout his career, artists copy Drake's style and sound (thanks to 40) to stay revelant. The issue isn't whether Drake stole the culture or not, the issue is that everyone who emulates Drake's style for popularity will steal the culture.More Life stands as a model for the UK grime sound instead of UK grime artists and that is major problem.</p>

	<p>Grime is a young a genre going through a revival in the UK. There are loads of artists, young and old, putting out quality music weekly across the whole range of the undefinitve grime sound. Skepta and Giggs alone do not define the grime sound. Period. Even more so, the grime sound is nothing without the culture. You can not have grime without clashes. You can not have grime without "Lord of Mics". You cannot have grime with radio shows. None of which were featured on More Life. Americans artists looking to capture the grime sound will look to More Life as an example and completely abandon these three pillars of grime. In turn, America will produce music, brand it as grime, without any of the culture that birthed the genre, and promote it to influence other country's music scenes. More Life has the potential to ruin the cultivation of grime.</p>

	<p>Instead of American artists trying to bring grime into the States, they should  bring the UK grime artists to the States and let them introduce grime in America's music scene. America's music influences every other country's music, but now is the time for America to be influenced. </p> ]]></content>
</document> 
